Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Moving Images Collection, ca. 1928-2001 UA.Film.Video
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Sports, I.
  - Football, 3.
    - Film, 957 items
      - 1972 West Virginia vs. Pitt (1st quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 353)
      - 1972 West Virginia vs. Pitt (3rd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 355)
      - 1972 West Virginia vs. Pitt (4th quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 349)
      - 1973 #1 Blue/Gold (reel 1), 16mm film Reel 1 Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 492)
      - 1973 #1 Blue/Gold (reel 2), 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 258)
      - 1973 #1 Blue/Gold (reel 3), 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 493)
      - 1973 #1 Blue/Gold (reel 4), 16mm film Reel 4 Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 494)
      - 1973 #2 Blue/Gold (reel 2), September 4, 1973; 16mm film Reel 2 Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 257)
      - 1973 Army vs. Pitt (1st quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 376)
      - 1973 Army vs. Pitt (2nd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 377)
      - 1973 Army vs. Pitt (3rd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 255)
      - 1973 Army vs. Pitt (4th quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 256)
      - 1973 Baylor vs. Pitt (1st half Offense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 249)
      - 1972 West Virginia vs. Pitt (2nd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 354)
      - 1973 Baylor vs. Pitt (1st half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 247)
      - 1973 Baylor vs. Pitt (2nd half Offense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 250)
      - 1973 Baylor vs. Pitt (2nd half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 248)
      - 1973 Boston College vs. Pitt (1st half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 374)
      - 1973 Boston College vs. Pitt (2nd half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 375)
      - 1973 Georgia vs. Pitt (2nd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 372)
      - 1973 Georgia vs. Pitt (3rd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 259)
      - 1973 Georgia vs. Pitt (4th quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 260)
      - 1973 Navy vs. Pitt (1st half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 254)
      - 1973 Navy vs. Pitt (2nd half Offense), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 379)
      - 1973 Navy vs. Pitt (2nd half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 378)
      - 1973 Northwestern vs. Pitt (1st half Offense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 243)
      - 1973 Northwestern vs. Pitt (1st half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 242)
      - 1973 Northwestern vs. Pitt (2nd half Offense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 244)
      - 1973 Northwestern vs. Pitt (2nd half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 251)
      - 1973 Syracuse vs. Pitt (2nd half Offense), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 373)
      - 1973 Tulane vs. Pitt (2nd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 261)
      - 1973 Tulane vs. Pitt (3rd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 262)
      - 1973 Tulane vs. Pitt (4th quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 263)
      - 1973 West Virginia vs. Pitt (1st half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 245)
      - 1973 West Virginia vs. Pitt (2nd half Defense), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 246)
      - 1974 Boston College vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 272)
      - 1974 Florida State vs. Pitt
      - 1974 Georgia Tech vs. Pitt (1st quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 380)
      - 1974 Georgia Tech vs. Pitt (2nd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 381)
      - 1974 Georgia Tech vs. Pitt (3rd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 382)
      - 1974 Georgia Tech vs. Pitt (4th quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 383)
      - 1974 Georgia Tech vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 384)
      - 1974 Navy vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 269)
      - 1974 North Carolina vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 264)
      - 1974 Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 266)
      - 1974 Notre Dame vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 267)
      - 1974 Penn State vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 273)
      - 1974 Southern California vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 268)
      - 1974 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 271)
      - 1974 Temple vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 270)
      - 1974 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 265)
      - 1975 Army vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 395)
      - 1975 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 396)
      - 1975 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 389)
      - 1975 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 391)
      - 1975 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 390)
      - 1975 Duke vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 388)
      - 1975 Duke vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 399)
      - 1975 Duke vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 398)
      - 1975 Duke vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 400)
      - 1975 Navy vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 393)
      - 1975 Oklahoma vs. Pitt, [DVD Available], 16mm film (4 reels - #392, 386, 387, 385) Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 392, 385-387)
      - 1975 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 397)
      - 1975 William and Mary vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/2 (Box 42, Reel 394)
      - 1976 Pitt vs. (Defense #2), 1969; 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 599)
      - 1976 Army vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 592)
      - 1976 Duke vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 418)
      - 1976 Duke vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 429)
      - 1976 Duke vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 428)
      - 1976 Georgia Tech vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 427)
      - 1976 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 600)
      - 1976 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 423)
      - 1976 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 421)
      - 1976 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 422)
      - 1976 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 604)
      - 1976 Miami vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 602)
      - 1976 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 603)
      - 1976 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 605)
      - 1976 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 409)
      - 1976 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 417)
      - 1976 Sugar Bowl (Defense #1), [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 420)
      - 1976 Sugar Bowl (Defense #2), [DVD Available], 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 419)
      - 1976 Syracuse vs. Pitt, 16mm film Reel 3 Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 591)
      - 1976 Temple vs. Pitt (1st quarter), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 415)
      - 1976 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 416)
      - 1976 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 601)
      - 1977 #1 West Virginia vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 411)
      - 1977 #1 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 410)
      - 1977 #2 Gator Bowl (2nd quarter), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 595)
      - 1977 #3 Varsity-Alumni Game, 16mm film Reel 1 Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 412)
      - 1977 #3 Varsity-Alumni Game, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 413)
      - 1977 #3 Varsity-Alumni Game, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 414)
      - 1977 Boston College vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 426)
      - 1977 Navy vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 425)
      - 1977 Tulane vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 424)
      - 1978 Temple vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 587)
      - 1979 #1 Fiesta Bowl, 16mm film Reel 4 Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 594)
      - 1979 "Got a Winner Again?", 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 861)
      - 1979 Boston College vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 586)
      - 1979 Cincinnati vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 588)
      - 1979 Navy vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 589)
      - 1979 North Carolina vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 590)
      - 1979 North Carolina vs. Pitt, September 22, 1979 (Box 42, Reel 1081)
      - 1979 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 598)
      - 1979 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 597)
      - 1979 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 596)
      - 1979 Temple vs. Pitt, 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 585)
      - 1979 Temple vs. Pitt, September 29, 1979 (Box 42, Reel 1082)
        Jackie Sherril Show
      - 1978 Temple vs. Pitt, September 22, 1978 (Box 42, Reel 1080)
        Played at Pitt Stadium. Reel contains quarters 1-3.
      - 1980 #1 Maryland vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 497)
      - 1980 #1 Maryland vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 500)
      - 1980 #2 Tennessee vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 499)
      - 1980 #2 Tennessee vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 488)
      - 1980 #3 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 485)
      - 1980 #3 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 487)
      - 1980 #3 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 489)
      - 1980 #4 Boston College vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 490)
      - 1980 #4 Boston College vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 491)
      - 1980 #5 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 486)
      - 1980 #3 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 501)
      - 1980 #6 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 502)
      - 1980 #6 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 498)
      - 1980 #7 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 496)
      - 1980 #7 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 495)
      - 1980 #8 Kansas vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 611)
      - 1980 #8 Kansas vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 593)
      - 1980 #9 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 478)
      - 1980 #9 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 475)
      - 1980 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 476)
      - 1980 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 479)
      - 1980 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 606)
      - 1980 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 612)
      - 1981 #1 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 609)
      - 1981 #1 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 619)
      - 1981 #1 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 627)
      - 1981 #1 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 620)
      - 1981 #2 Cincinnati vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 482)
      - 1981 #2 Cincinnati vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 484)
      - 1981 #2 Cincinnati vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 483)
      - 1981 #2 Cincinnati vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 474)
      - 1981 #3 Illinois vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 460)
      - 1981 #3 Illinois vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 480)
      - 1981 #3 Illinois vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 461)
      - 1981 #3 Illinois vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 481)
      - 1981 #4 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 607)
      - 1981 #4 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 610)
      - 1981 #4 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 608)
      - 1981 #4 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 617)
      - 1981 #5 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 624)
      - 1981 #5 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 621)
      - 1981 #5 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 622)
      - 1981 #5 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 466)
      - 1981 #6 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 467)
      - 1981 #6 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 469)
      - 1981 #6 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 468)
      - 1981 #6 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 470)
      - 1981 #7 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 613)
      - 1981 #7 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 615)
      - 1981 #7 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 614)
      - 1981 #7 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 616)
      - 1981 #8 Florida vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 625)
      - 1981 #8 Florida vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 618)
      - 1981 #8 Florida vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 626)
      - 1981 #8 Florida vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 623)
      - 1981 #9 Florida State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 643)
      - 1981 #9 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 648)
      - 1981 #9 Florida State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 647)
      - 1981 #9 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 649)
      - 1981 #10 Boston College vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 639)
      - 1981 #10 Boston College vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 641)
      - 1981 #10 Boston College vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 640)
      - 1981 #10 Boston College vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 642)
      - 1981 #11 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 462)
      - 1981 #11 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 464)
      - 1981 #11 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 463)
      - 1981 #11 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 465)
      - 1981 #12 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 473)
      - 1981 #12 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 458)
      - 1981 #12 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 471)
      - 1981 #12 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 477)
      - 1981 #12 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 459)
      - 1981 #12 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 472)
      - 1982 #2 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 650)
      - 1982 #2 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 645)
      - 1982 #2 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 644)
      - 1982 #2 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 646)
      - 1982 #3 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 629)
      - 1982 #3 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 633)
      - 1982 #3 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 628)
      - 1982 #4 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 630)
      - 1982 #4 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 632)
      - 1982 #4 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 631)
      - 1982 #4 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 634)
      - 1982 #5 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 637)
      - 1982 #5 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 635)
      - 1982 #5 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 638)
      - 1982 #5 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 636)
      - 1982 #6 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 453)
      - 1982 #6 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 454)
      - 1982 #6 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 455)
      - 1982 #6 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 456)
      - 1982 #7 Florida State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 448)
      - 1982 #7 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 450)
      - 1982 #7 Florida State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 449)
      - 1982 #7 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 451)
      - 1982 #8 Illinois vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 433)
      - 1982 #8 Illinois vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 447)
      - 1982 #8 Illinois vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 434)
      - 1982 #8 Illinois vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 457)
      - 1982 #9 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 654)
      - 1982 #9 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 446)
      - 1982 #9 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 653)
      - 1982 #9 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 445)
      - 1982 #10 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 440)
      - 1982 #10 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 432)
      - 1982 #10 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 441)
      - 1982 #10 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 439)
      - 1982 #11 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 442)
      - 1982 #11 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 443)
      - 1982 #11 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 444)
      - 1982 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 452)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 658)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 659)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 666)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 668)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 665)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 667)
      - 1983 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 669)
      - 1983 #2 Florida State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 670)
      - 1983 #2 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 663)
      - 1983 #2 Florida State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 671)
      - 1983 #2 Florida State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 664)
      - 1983 #3 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 651)
      - 1983 #3 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 656)
      - 1983 #3 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 655)
      - 1983 #3 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 430)
      - 1983 #4 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 437)
      - 1983 #4 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 515)
      - 1983 #4 Army vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 438)
      - 1983 #4 Army vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 516)
      - 1983 #5 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 511)
      - 1983 #5 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 507)
      - 1983 #5 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 512)
      - 1983 #5 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 508)
      - 1983 #5 Penn State vs. Pitt (Close-up), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 510)
      - 1983 #6 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 661)
      - 1983 #6 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 652)
      - 1983 #6 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 662)
      - 1983 #6 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 660)
      - 1983 #7 Tennessee vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 688)
      - 1983 #7 Tennessee vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 687)
      - 1983 #7 Tennessee vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 684)
      - 1983 #7 Tennessee vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 686)
      - 1983 #8 Maryland vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 685)
      - 1983 #8 Maryland vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 674)
      - 1983 #8 Maryland vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 673)